(Howard:)Hang on,
the sensor's picking up something.
(Howard:)Turn your head back.
(Penny:)You rat bastard.
HOWARD:
Told you the sensor would work.
(Scene:)Hi.
(Penny:)You deliberately stuck me with Sheldon.
Come on, I had to.
You see what he's like.
SHELDON:
Penny? Penny, I'm hungry.
(Penny:)It's okay, sweetie. Good news.
(Penny:)- Leonard's home.
- No.
- Here you go, good luck, bye.
- Oh, wait, wait.
SHELDON: Leonard? I'm hungry.
- Wait. Penny, take me with you.
SHELDON:
Leonard?
(Sheldon:)I want grilled cheese.
(Sheldon:)Do you think Penny will come here
and take care of us?
(Leonard:)I don't think Penny's
ever coming here again.
(Sheldon:)I'm very congested.
Yeah? So?
(Sheldon:)Can you go to the kitchen and get me
the turkey baster labeled, "Mucus"?
(Leonard:)If I stand, I'll vomit.
(Sheldon:)Under the sink. Yellow Tupperware bowl.